right I already did one that was very
rested I just pleaded it since no one
popped it doesn't really matter and then
I went on Facebook because why wouldn't
I customer I live and someone posted
this and you know there's just so much
here I'm part of a lot of like
attachment parenting groups and
therefore a lot of my friends are also
part of attachment parenting stuff and
it's the philosophy I tried to follow
with my baby when she was a baby now I'm
probably more of the leg
but not neglect parents cuz it's what
I'm capable of and here's the thing that
was posted it's a picture so in this
family we are trauma-informed we connect
before we correct
we understand behavior is communication
we teach self-regulation we allow
do-overs we think camp instead of won't
we empathize when someone when someone's
flipping their lid we make repair we
breathe deeply we love even more deeply
and we know healing happens in
relationships that's by attachment in
trauma Network and that's very much the
parenting style I try to implement I
fail horribly at it constantly and I
think that's a piece of it that we need
to do this for ourselves as well as our
children we need to understand that our
behavior is also communication like I
have anxiety and I flip out all the time
and I'm like okay like the more I
realize that's why I'm doing it instead
of making myself wrong about it just
correct it repair it like move forth
like it's like yeah I do yell a lot and
I don't even know if I'm not supposed to
like it's anger and it's getting out in
a way that's not violence in a way
that's not um hopefully scary to my kids
like she's scared of me
and anyway like it's like it works like
it's not this that's not but it's it's
allowing myself to be this and that's
that's to me we need to do this in the
world not just for children
great we raised an entire generation
like this every child that would be that
would be amazing but the truth is every
adult can't raise their child this way
because we are not like I'm in the I'm
not quite capable of this and I love I
love the concept of calling people in
and you have no idea how to do it like
I'm like all I know how to do is call
people oh dear I'd like my whole life
it's like it's you know smokings bad for
you it's like who didn't know smoking
was bad for them if they're smoking a
cigarette they know you know like I mean
is not Vera when I was a vegetarian I'm
not a vegetarian really and calling
people out and it never changes people's
minds it might make me feel a little bit
better but I know with that it doesn't
change people's minds I don't know if it
ever has and I think that what is
powerful is calling people in but there
isn't really a lot of why do something
how to actually do that it's more of
like a feeling right and I think that
coming back to love is and this I this
concept like I think this thing is
calling people it's your children but
like calling them and instead of
outright the whole point is we
understand that behavior is
communication that when someone is doing
something and they have this concept I
don't know which tribe in Africa or
whether that's just a myth anyway I like
the tribe that the communities like when
they do something wrong instead of
punishing them they surround them and
show them how loved they are like if we
had a criminal justice system that take
that but you need a criminal justice
system like it's the earning but both it
like we based if we raised an entire
generation like this we wouldn't need it
it's like it's automatic so what
attachment parenting is it's like okay
the more you we raise peaceful kids the
bohr they don't need to do a world in
which is correcting where maybe we
weren't so peacefully raised and I think
that's perfect too because I've
experienced one of experience it's made
me who I am in order to have more
compassion for my kid and pass on less
trauma probably not zero but less when
my parents did the same they passed on
less trauma to me than they had right
like it's
it's improving and but improving in a
incremental way that's not like an
all-or-nothing because we can't be
everything we can't be perfect I'm a big
being perfect is perfect how horrible
would it be if you had a perfect parent
like a perfect it never did anything
wrong how would you know how to correct
yourself when you're wrong
honestly ridiculous thank goodness I'm
not a perfect fairy but so like raised
our kids that way is what this is all
about but also happy not for ourselves
that like there's things that I truly
can't do it's not that I won't do them
it's that I can like I'm like my brain
will not retain information like it used
to read Tina I like stupid makes my
world fall apart and you know I can
handle the big stuff like I am handling
the big stuff which is partly why I
can't have the little stuff it's like
okay like braiding tumors in poverty
like personally and then like globally
it's like poverty and climate change all
of these big huge things that because I
have a solution or like Wayne heavy on
my shoulders and and I'm just like going
with the flow and not having it weigh
heavily on my shoulders I'm like okay
this is gonna unfold in its right time
you just have to be doing what you can
do it I know I'm not a hundred percent
there I know I'm not like I'm like oh I
could just like lives through myself
constantly I could just I'm not being
vulnerable enough I'm not being you know
something enough and it's like no yeah
but you're not it's not that you won't
it's that you can't like you're not
there yet that doesn't feel safe to you
yet that doesn't feel stress-free to you
so you're not there yet that's fine
so having this for ourselves and I will
link what I'm actually this picture it's
just a Facebook post but I'll link it in
the UM the comments er yeah comments or
description probably description makes
more sense in case there's like a flood
of comments on this this video more
importantly though I think we need to
have that for other adults which I said
that yet but it was like kids ourselves
and more importantly for other adults
because we need to allow to offerors we
need to allow ourselves to not be and
everyone else to like make mistakes we
have to understand that people can't do
things not necessarily they won't racist
sexist homophobic people
it's not that they won't see the world
your way they can't see the world your
way and yelling at them to see it your
way it's not making the world's any
better and so and I get that I still
yeah but I'm still giving yellow I don't
know if I can come at Trump would love
when he is destroying families and our
whole world but I also understand that
it's not changing the world or the way
we're currently doing it and so just
again compassion for myself I know I'm
not this perfect parent I know that I
have to have compassion for myself when
I fail here and same with with the world
like it's like okay if we can have this
not this exact one but this is our like
ethos our community or connection or
culture of like okay you're allowed to
make mistakes and then repair them
you're allowed to when someone's
flipping their lid we empathize with
them right like we get that that's an
emotion needs to kind of process do its
thing and then go and if they do
something during that process that is
not okay that they do need to go and
repair it after and that's part of
raising a kids teaching them that peace
too which is a huge piece is going
repairing nurse like like you know
when I yelled at you yesterday that was
not me at my best
let's try to I don't I don't ever like
I'll never do that again
like that's clearly a lie I'm gonna try
to work on that I'm gonna do that less
and less as we go as you get older and
you antagonize see me more and more I
will try to do that less and less and
I'm I am a crumpled sheet that you know
it feels like I'm yelling at her Laura
more it's like it's actually staying to
but she's getting worse and worse she's
getting older so it's like all right and
I am getting a little better at it the
more I meditate the more I let go of my
addictions which are also a piece of it
and not like force myself to let go of
them because that doesn't work not like
I'm a very all-or-nothing person and in
that it means like oh I'm on a diet I
eat one thing so like it's over it's
like you know I'm going cold turkey now
it's over because I did it one time it's
like no or you could find a way to like
minimize it in your life to reduce it
with each stuff because that feels safe
to me in a way that cold turkey never
has in with whatever right like having
my whole house clean just has an owner
that's ever happened but then one things
out of place it's like it's nice well
I'll go to hell like I'm very much that
personality and realizing that's not the
way for me to make the best changes
because then something's always gonna go
wrong so then it fit all falls apart you
haven't gotten anywhere and allowing
like okay you made a commitment and you
didn't follow through on it that's okay
that was one day recommit tomorrow
frequent the next day and it's it is
helping me evolve and the more I'm there
without holding on to it without making
that the only way like no you can still
have to like I don't know it's a it's a
process but this piece of like we allow
back to the actual topic we teach
self-regulation we allow do-overs we
think can't instead of won't we
empathize and people are flip either
when did we make repairs we breathe
deeply and we love more deeply and I
think that's the key is to love people
where they are and I don't know when you
can see the world as a kid and I do it's
one of the things having my brain injury
like the actual process of getting brain
injured because it was my brain swelling
after brain surgery which made me feel
like a toddler and gave me the
perspective years later when I became a
parent like oh that's what she's going
through
I have less sympathy for her now that
she's five and a half that when she was
two and three because my brain was it
two or three year-olds when I went
through that it's like oh yeah you don't
know how to like express your ideas yet
you don't know you just like the world
isn't working for me like it's like okay
I get that I can have sympathy though
it's into my better times I can have
sympathy in those moments now soon
because I can still see right but even
in that process and like everyone in the
world became baby like young kids to me
like you can see their little kid
self-clean like you know nine-year-old
grandmother's like oh that's my baby
like that's I don't know there was
something something there it's still
there it's like we're we are still kids
in so many ways like when you my kid
says like racist homophobic stuff like
great um we need to correct that it's I
don't make her wrong for it like I get
that it's just her exploring her world
right sometimes I make her really for it
sometimes particular because it
like provokes me but I'm like okay well
that's not the best that's I would not
suggest that is the way of dealing with
it that scene even if it's like you know
a 40 year old full-grown man who's like
five times my size it's still a little
kid like it's still a little kid who is
who is like people think it better I
don't know like it's still all of those
emotions and all of that triggering and
all of it because the truth is you can't
be a grown-up mind and not and still
like hold all those racist thoughts not
without letting them go right like we're
all racists or all homophobic and as we
try to be less and less and less we
become less and less and less less you
just want to ignore that altogether
I don't know but like kid like all of
that together oh yeah we're just gonna
post this because this need to be
perfect no one needs to be perfect
something I won't make these videos
better so I can't make those videos
better all right take care